http://antlersbyklaus.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy at Antlers by Klaus.
We value the trust you place in Antlers by Klaus, and we want you to be aware of the safeguards we have in place to respect your privacy. The below policy tells you about the information we gather about you and how we use it. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at info@AntlersbyKlaus.com.
Types of personal information we may gather:
Antlers by Klaus gathers personal information from you in order to provide superior service, communicate offers on merchandise and services which we believe will be of interest to you, customize our communications to you, administer our business, and improve your shopping experience. The following are examples of the personal information we gather from you.
Purchases: When you place an order, you give us your name, address, phone number and/or email address plus payment information.
Non-Purchases: There may be instances when you are not making a purchase at Antlers by Klaus and you give us your name, address, phone number and/or email address, and where applicable, payment information, or when somebody else gives us your name, address, phone number and/or email address, and where applicable, payment information. Some situations when this may occur are when you return or exchange merchandise, receive a gift from Antlers by Klaus or enter a contest or participate in a promotion or survey sponsored by Antlers by Klaus.
Personal Shopping Account: If you create a Personal Shopping Account with us so that you may place orders more conveniently, you authorize us to store your name and shipping address(es), and payment information.
Email updates – When you subscribe to receive Antlers by Klaus email updates featuring exclusive offers (like free shipping), product news, special discounts, contests and more, we require your email address. You can unsubscribe anytime.
How we use personal information:
We ask you for certain kinds of personal information in order to provide you with the services you request and to process and deliver your order. We also may use your personal information to provide you with customized communications and keep you updated on the latest promotions or products that may interest you.
In addition, our site utilizes ‘cookies.’ Cookies do not gather any of your personally identifiable information. They do allow us to provide you with a more personalized shopping experience and enable you to fully interact with and complete your transaction on our site.
Antlers by Klaus shares its customer information with its affiliated company, Antlers by Klaus. We also may share your information with our business partners in order to provide you with certain services. Finally, we do make our mailing list available to carefully screened companies whose products or services might interest you. If you prefer to have your name withheld, please call us toll-free at (715) 246-5240 or send an email to info@AntlersbyKlaus.com.
In addition, Antlers by Klaus cooperates in advertising member networks with other consumer entities where we may communicate your personal information so that select members may inform you about products or services that might interest you. If you prefer to have your name withheld, please call us toll-free at (715) 246-5240 or send an email to info@AntlersbyKlaus.com.
If you first became a Antlers by Klaus customer through a transaction with our parent company, Antlers by Klaus, we adhere to Antlers by Klaus’ privacy policy with respect to any personal information that you may share with us and with the business partners that help this site function or assist us in fulfilling your order.
For more about your privacy at Antlers by Klaus, please call us toll-free at (715) 246-5240 or email us, including your name and mailing address, at customerservice@AntlersbyKlaus.com.
Along with respecting your privacy, Antlers by Klaus diligently strives to keep your personal information safe and secure. (Please see our Security Policy.)
What are cookies?
‘Cookies’ are small data files that one of our servers sends to your computer via your Web browser when you connect with our Web site. Their primary function is to help us remember you by tracking your browsing sessions, which enables us to collect non-personally identifiable information (such as your IP address, browser type, and domain name, etc.), and provide you with a more relevant shopping experience.
How we use cookies:
We use cookies to help process your order through our website and to provide you with a personalized shopping experience. To place an order and complete your transaction on AntlersbyKlaus.com, you must have ‘cookies’ enabled on your Web browser. (If you don’t want to enable cookies but would like to place an order, please call us toll free at (715) 246-5240.) You must also have cookies turned on in order to create a personal account on AntlersbyKlaus.com and to access that online account.
Cookies also help us:
determine which features and tools you use, and which pages you visit on Antlers by Klaus.com
remember which items you’ve placed in your shopping bag
enable you to check out faster if you’ve created an account with us. In addition, we use cookies to provide you with advertisements and promotions across various other websites from Antlers by Klaus based on your web browsing behavior and to similarly allow other entities, in which you may be interested, to provide you with their advertisements and promotions across various other websites. If you would like more information about this specific practice or would like to opt out of participating in this particular practice, please email us at customerservice@AntlersbyKlaus.com.
If you have any concerns about leaving cookies on your computer for extended periods, you can delete them using your browser preferences or privacy menus.
Our Business Partners
In order to ship and track merchandise, we make your name and address available to certain companies that help us provide you with those services.
Mailing List Preference
If you do not want to have your name shared with non-affiliated companies, or if you no longer wish to receive Antlers by Klaus emails, please call (715) 246-5240. You can also contact us via email at info@Antlers by Klaus.com. Please include your name and mailing address in the message. If you would like to no longer receive emails from Antlers by Klaus, please unsubscribe or click on the ‘unsubscribe’ link included in all emails sent by Antlers by Klaus.
Children’s Privacy at Antlers by Klaus
Antlers by Klaus does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children’s products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use our website with the involvement of a parent or guardian. Moreover, Antlers by Klaus is concerned about the safety of children. Occasionally, Antlers by Klaus may conduct promotions or contests that allow children under the age of 13 to participate. In those instances, we will use reasonable efforts to obtain verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from these participants. Rest assured that Antlers by Klaus will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without making reasonable efforts to obtain verifiable parental consent. In addition, Antlers by Klaus will not condition a child’s participation in an event on the provision of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in the activity, and Antlers by Klaus will not sell that information and will only use that information in the manner that we disclose in the promotion or contest. In those instances where Antlers by Klaus collects personal information from a child, that child’s parents or guardians will have the ability to review the information provided by their child by sending an email message to customerservice@AntlersbyKlaus.com or to the email address listed on the Antler byKlaus.com web page that collected their child’s information. Parents or guardians may also request that Antlers by Klaus not make contact with their child. If such a parental request is received, Antlers by Klaus will make all reasonable efforts to make sure that no communications are sent to the child.
Terms of Use
By accessing or using any features on AntlersbyKlaus.com, you agree to be bound by these terms of service. We may periodically change these terms without providing prior notice. So, we recommend that you read these terms carefully each time you use this website.
Please note that all antler/horn scores and related information is presented as accurately as possible.
However, Antlers By Klaus is not responsible for misprints or received misinformation.
Disputes
Applicable Law
Any dispute relating to the Antlers by Klaus.com website or use or inability to use AntlersbyKlaus.com website (collectively, ‘Dispute’) will be governed by the laws of the State of Wisconsin, without regard to (i) its conflict of law provisions, (ii) the 1980 United Nations Convention on Contracts for the International Sale of Goods, or (iii) any provision of the Uniform Computer Information Transaction Act as it may be enacted in Wisconsin or any other jurisdiction. Antlers by Klaus will not be liable for and you may not recover consequential, punitive, special, incidental, and/or indirect damages from any claim relating to your use of the AntlersbyKlaus.com website.
Mandatory Arbitration
Any Dispute shall be submitted to confidential arbitration in Madison, Wisconsin, except that, to the extent you have in any manner violated or threatened to violate our intellectual property rights, we may seek injunctive or any other appropriate relief in any state or federal court in the State of Wisconsin, and you consent to exclusive jurisdiction and venue in such courts. Arbitration of any and all Disputes shall be conducted in accordance with the American Arbitration Association rules with a three judge panel. The arbitration award shall be binding and may be entered as a judgment in any court of competent jurisdiction.
No Class Actions
To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, no arbitration under these terms shall be joined to an arbitration involving any other party subject to these terms, whether through class arbitration or otherwise.
MOST POPULAR THIS MONTH
Cody Robbins Buck
Kansas King Sheds
Whitetail Deer Capes
Milo Hanson Buck
Whitmire Buck
Satisfaction Guarantee
FAQs
Copyright 2018, Kaiser Lebrecht, LLC / Antlers by Klaus.
All rights reserved.
All Images and Text are protected by U.S. and International Copyright Law.
Click here to see our video
